You two murderers,
I gave you the identity of Lin Jiming
and everything that comes with it.
Wake up
and be a good heir to the Lin family.
Don't go crazy here.
What?
Not happy?
Then you'd better have the guts
to take away what's most important to me now.
Can you do that?
Dear son,
who do you think you are?
The heir to the Lin Group?
The biological son of Lin Muyun?
You're not.
You are the child of Wu Zhanshan.
You are the child of your mother, Wen Shiyi,
and his distant cousin, Wu Zhanshan.
Mr. Lin,
you can't be discharged yet.
Mr. Lin.
Xintian!
Xintian, open the door!
I know you're in there.
Can you hear me out?
Xintian!
Open the door!
I know you're in there!
Xintian.
Xintian, open the door.
There's nothing
to explain between us.
Not even a little?
There's only blood debt between us.
Goodbye, Mr. Lin.
Oh, no.
Mr. Wu.
Goodbye, Mr. Lin.
Oh, no.
Mr. Wu.
Who am I?
Wu Zhanshan's son,
Wen Shiyi's puppet,
or
the enemy
she wants to kill?
Mr. Wen,
don't worry.
I have already instructed Zhou Man.
She wouldn't dare to say anything.
Okay.
Got it.
Mr. Wen,
what's going on with Mr. Lin?
The company can't be leaderless.
The IPO is stalled.
We need a solution.
Yeah.
If this continues,
everyone's interests will be damaged.
Please calm down.
Listen to me.
I understand
your feelings.
First,
I have some sad news to tell you.
Our chairman,
the founder,
my husband, Mr. Lin Muyun
passed away
due to illness
the other day.
What?
How could this happen?
What's going on?
When did this happen?
Later,
a funeral committee will be set up
to arrange the funeral affairs of Chairman Lin.
As for Jiming,
he was greatly affected by his father's death.
At present,
his mental state
is extremely unstable.
He is unable to perform
any management duties.
Of course,
there are also
some people with ulterior motives
who are inciting
and bewitching him.
Just like the lawyer
he hired before,
whose background is unclear
and purpose is not pure.
He used his position
and improper means
to get close to Jiming,
disrupting the order of the company.
He even
sowed discord between us.
Jiming is young
and was temporarily deceived,
which led to today's situation.
As for this kind of person,
we Lin's Group
will never tolerate.
Mr. Wen,
I think your statement
is unfair.
Yaru,
this is not the place for you to speak.
Everyone,
during Guan's employment,
all the cases she handled
were done with neat and tidy.
She helped the company avoid huge risks
and potential losses.
Her professional ability and performance
are obvious to all of us.
To blame
Mr. Lin's personal emotions
on a dedicated and responsible
legal counsel who has already resigned,
I think
it's not only unfair,
but also
unconvincing.
Yaru,
please sit down.
Don't be childish.
Director Liu,
what we are discussing now
is the management
and responsibility of the company,
not a child's game.
Mr. Wen,
you mentioned ulterior motives
and improper means.
May I ask
if there is concrete evidence?
If not,
is it appropriate to publicly accuse
in such a setting?
Liu Yaru,
be mindful of your position.
Since
the company has invited me to attend this meeting,
I have the responsibility and obligation
to uphold the company's fairness and reputation.
I believe
the most important thing now
is to stabilize the situation
and solve the problem,
not
to find a scapegoat
and engage in personal attacks.
What we should be focusing on now
is how to get the company back on track,
not publicly accusing
someone who isn't even here.
That's all, everyone.
Given the current
emergency situation,
in accordance with the company's articles of association
and the relevant clauses of the shareholder agreement,
I propose
and have obtained
the joint support of
some major shareholders,
that effective immediately,
I, Wen Shiyi,
will serve as the acting Chairman and CEO of the Group,
until Mr. Lin Jiming
fully recovers,
or a more
suitable permanent
solution is found.
I agree.
Besides,
there's another thing.
It's about the future ownership
structure of the Lin Group.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is
the will of Lin Muyun,
the founder of Lin Group,
signed
in the presence of
two independent lawyers
three years ago.
The will
stated that all the shares
of Lin Group
and
all personal movable and
immovable properties
unconditionally
to his wife,
that is,
Ms. Wen Shiyi.
So,
I will do my best
to lead Lin Group
out of difficulties
and return to its former glory.
Yaru
What does Chairman Liu want to do?
How can you talk to your brother like that?
I haven't asked you yet.
Why did you suddenly come back?
Why can't I come back?
Tell me the truth.
Did you and Wen Shiyi
reach some agreement?
Yaru
You shouldn't have said that.
People who don't know the truth
may think that I asked you to say that.
Fine.
From now on,
you are you,
and I am me.
What are you talking about?
Am I not your brother?
I just want to warn you.
Be careful of Wen Shiyi.
Don't drag our Liu family into this.
You...
Yaru
Let me explain.
Big news!
Shareholders' meeting.
She...
Have some water and take your time.
What's going on?
Wen Shiyi
launched a surprise attack.
Lin Muyun passed away,
and Lin Jiming is mentally unstable and unable to fulfill his duties.
Now she's temporarily
taking over as chairman
and CEO of the Lin Group.
Lin Muyun passed away?
Yes.
And there's more.
She
presented a will
at the shareholders' meeting.
It's Lin Muyun's will,
claiming
that Lin Muyun left all his shares and assets
to her.
Legally,
Lin Jiming is completely out.
Now the Lin Group is entirely owned by Wen Shiyi.
She's so scary.
She can do this to Lin Jiming,
she...
she can do this to my brother.
But my brother is still foolishly
running back to support her.
Tian,
what should we do?
She is cleaning up the battlefield,
and also showing off to us.
But she made a mistake.
She has pushed everyone to the edge.
Yaru,
if you want to protect the Liu family,
just relying on defense
is not enough.
We must cooperate more thoroughly.
What do you want to do?
[This morning,]
[the headquarters of Lin Group was crowded with media,]
[and the atmosphere was tense.]
[Many senior executives and shareholders returned in a hurry]
[to attend this sudden shareholders' meeting.]
[It was announced that]
[Mr. Lin Muyun, the founder of Lin Group,]
[has passed away due to illness.]
[The group will be]
[taken over by his wife,]
[Wen Shiyi, the vice chairman,]
[who will take over all duties from his son Lin Jiming.]
[At the same time,]
[Lin Muyun's will was made public,]
[confirming Ms. Wen Shiyi]
[as the sole legal heir of the group.]
[It is reported that]
[Mr. Lin Muyun]
[was known for his foresight.]
Wen Shiyi,
do you think you can rest assured
by eliminating the heir and forging the will?
Have you forgotten
that you are not only
standing on the ruins of Lin Jiming,
but also on the countless mines you buried.
Now,
it's my turn
to blow them up.